I'll show it a brief story of your conception, so probably five years also back, oh no, six,
maybe even seven. I got into the space of machine learning, looking for what we now
call a generator by eye. So I got a sort of a bit of a handle on basic systems and how
they would integrate fast forward to when chat GPT-2 was sort of source compilable. It
built a version of that and it was quite amazed by it spitting out some sentences. And then we cut
through and studying doing all the things using AI, then over the summer I was building a confidential
document handling OCR pipeline that would pick up handwriting and like art scores from the
identified surveys from the emotional regulation which are now sort of updated to temporality,
management, more so, but that's not a standing title. Moving on, that I went away for a week to
Woodford Folk Festival and had a pretty wild time there and one of the nights that I had been
up all night, it was back at the campsite drinking wine and smoking a cigarette six in the morning
and this lovely lady wondered over and we ended up going and doing some yoga and sharing a
wonderful morning together and have kept in touch since then and there's a consequence of that
interaction have noticed a vast increase in my drive which I'm attributing at least partially to
resonance. Obviously there's implicit intelligence underlying the whole thing and these are only
the facets that I care to name at the moment. That drive was instantiated when I discovered
OpenClaw and have been building the systems that are since. I'm going to stop the note there
because I'm afraid of how long it's gotten already and we'll continue one later, prompt me if it
strikes you.